

Manikandan S

Working Professional

Chennai, Tamil Nadu India

Fmail ID eventhiswillpassmk95@gmail.com

Mobile Number 8681063655

Skills/Languages Known

Hard Skills

CSS HTML

Node.js

Soft Skills

Javascript

Creative

Problem Solver

Area of Interest

IT and Software

Programming

Portfolio

https://adorable-unicorn-0481ea.netlify.app/



https://github.com/manis6595/manis6595

Summary

In my previous roles, I successfully Work As Team Leader in BPO Sector . This experience, coupled with my commitment to continuous learning, has equipped me with a solid foundation for entering the IT sector. I have recently completed Full Stack Developer with MERN Course to further enhance my technical skills.

Educational Qualifications

O Diploma in Information Technology

MSPVL Polytechnic College

Apr, 2012 - Apr, 2014

Grade: 85%

A Diploma in IT typically covers a range of subjects, including programming languages, database management, networking, and web development

O Class 12th - (TN HSC Board)

Punitha Arulappar Hr Sec School

Apr, 2011 - Apr, 2012

Grade: 75%

12th-grade computer science department can vary depending on the specific curriculum and educational institution typically focus on advanced topics in computer science, building upon the foundations laid in earlier grades.

Professional Experience

O Team Leader

Hathway Cable & Data Com Ltd | Billing

Aug, 2019 - Present

Handling 1.5L Existing Customers base with 90 Agents Collect the Fixed Target Amount From this Renewal Customers Maintain the Feedback for Unpaid Accounts & Given the Exact Reason, RCA to the Management in every MBR

Data Entry Operator

Computer Age Management Services Private Limited | MNC

Aug, 2017 - Jun, 2019

· A Data Entry Operator compiles and verifies data to ensure accuracy while appropriately formatting it. • Maintain and update customers' database.

Reach out to me at

Email ID eventhiswillpassmk95@gmail.com

Mobile Number 8681063655

Portfolio





https://github.com/manis6595/manis6595

Professional Experience

O Business Executive.

Vertex Customer Solution India Private Limited | BPO Jun, 2014 - Sep, 2017

• Handle Inbound customer complaints,